Philippines being a former colony and then also now being a neo-colony, there are still U.S. military bases in the Philippines now.
It really impacted the Philippines economically, and there are these things called OFWs.
They are overseas Filipino workers, which is a term that is used by the government because these people have to go overseas because they can't find a living in the Philippines.
And then about $200 billion a year are remittances by these overseas Filipino workers sending it back home.
Like in Dubai.
Exactly. And so that actually is my story. I am a son of an OFW. I was born in Saudi Arabia.
And for the first four years of my life, I barely saw my mother to the point when she would come back.
I would tell her she's not my mom and it's actually my aunts are my mom.
And so that is like the consequence of U.S. imperialism personally.
Does she bring?
No.
no.